# Gamaliel Lamadrid Perez

| San Luis Rio Colorado, Sonora, Mexico. 83458 | (+52) 653-155-7538 | gamaliel.lp05@gmail.com |

Web portfolio: https://gamaliel-developer.github.io/

### **Professional Profile**

I am a graduate of the software development and management engineering career with 3 years of experience in web and mobile development, including the time at university where practical projects were always carried out both in teams and individually. This has enabled me to work well in teams and to work under software development methodologies. I focus mainly on mobile development but I am open to other areas in the development field such as web, both Front-end or Back-end.

## **Experience**

### BACK-END DEVELOPER (INTERNAL) | BRIDGESTUDIO MX | APRIL 2023 - AUGUST 2023

- **My tasks** involved backend activities focused on API management, creating CRUD operations for the project, and developing endpoints for their respective tests to be used in the front-end.
- **My achievements** were adapting and solving most of my programming problems or conflicts despite it not being my strongest area.

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER (INTERNAL) | WISHAFT | SEPTEMBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

- **My tasks** consisted of carrying out the assigned activities for the week, mainly developing front-end and a bit of back-end using the Flutter language.
- **My achievements** were efficiently completing my project modules and fixing visual front-end bugs, as well as helping other projects while continuing to work on my assigned project.

### **Education**

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT AND MANAGEMENT ENGINEERING | UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA DE SAN LUIS RIO COLORADO (TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY OF SAN LUIS RIO COLORADO).

September 2019 - August 2023

At university, I have worked with servers and practiced web and mobile application development, both front-end and back-end. I have also participated in functional university projects for websites and mobile applications, using SQL and NoSQL databases in a team development environment.

### Skills

- Knowledge and management of APIs
- ADs integration
- Knowledge in the RTMP protocol
- SQL and NoSQL Database Management

#### **FRONT-END**

• CSS - HTML - React Native - Flutter - Angular - JavaScript - React.js

## **BACK-END**

• PHP – Node.js – Laravel – Dart

# Languages

• English: B1